Guide to the North Carolina Mutual Life Insurance Company Archives, 1850, 1888-2000s and undated, bulk 1920-2008 RL.00936
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Printed Materials, 1903-2008 and undated; 1920s-1990s; 51 boxes
  The substantial clippings file was assembled by the Public Relations Department, and is arranged topically in its original sequence; there are significant amounts of materials on the civil rights movement and on Durham history.
  There are also oversize sections at the end of each subseries chiefly housing newspapers and other serials; early whole issues as well as single pages of Durham newspapers can be found here, as well as newspapers from elsewhere, and issues of mainstream magazines such as Ebony. The Non-NCM subseries in addition contains a large sub-grouping of print items related to Durham's historically black North Carolina Central University (NCCU), including campus newspapers and events programs.
  Series, subseries, and their files are further described in this collection guide.
  - North Carolina Mutual Life Insurance Company Serials, 1903-1998
    Series comprises internal North Carolina Mutual serial publications, arranged alphabetically by title, then chronologically. Consists primarily of nearly complete runs of three company publications: The Mutual (1903, 1923-1929), The Whetstone (1924-1998), and The Weekly Review (1925-1998). Some large runs of issues are housed in original binders. One binder with mixed contents contains various samples of NCM publications, including an issue of The Whetstone (second quarter 1963); two issues of The Mutual; a pamphlet about the origins and history of the company, dated November 23, 1921; and the proceedings of the Annual Agents' Conference of 1920. A fourth publication is The Hotline (1988-1997). Listings in the collection guide include oversize material, found at the end of the series.
    - The Durham Reformer, Vol 13, No. 13 (two pages, pieces lacking), 1911 July 27 (Box OV59)
    - The Hotline, 1988-1997 (Box 137)
    - The North Carolina Mutual cover, 1903 Sept., clippings 1906 Jan. (Box 137)
    - The North Carolina Mutual, four partial issues, 1903-1906, 1912 (Box OV59)
    - The Mutual, 1923 June, 1923 Nov., 1924 Apr., 1927 Apr., 1929 (Box 137)
    - Newsorama, 1960-1961 (Box 137)
    - The Review, 1933-1966 Sept., 11 folders (Box 137)
    - The Review, 1966 Oct.-1985 Sept., 15 folders (Box 138)
    - The Review, 1986-1998, 19 folders (Box 139)
    - The Review (bound issues), 1956-1957 June, 3 binders (Box 140)
    - The Review (bound issues), 1957 July-1959 June, 4 binders (Box 141)
    - The Review (bound issues), 1960-1961, 4 binders (Box 142)
    - The Review (bound issues), 1962-1963, 3 binders (Box 143)
    - The Review (bound issues), 1963-1964 Dec., 4 binders (Box 144)
    - The Review (bound issues), 1965, 3 binders (Box 145)
    - The Review (bound issues), 1966, 2 binders (Box 146)
    - The Review (bound issues), 1967, 2 binders (Box 147)
    - The Review (bound issues), 1968, 2 binders (Box 148)
    - The Review (bound issues), 1969-1970, 3 binders (Box 149)
    - The Review (bound issues), 1971-1972, 3 binders (Box 150)
    - The Review (bound issues), 1972-1974, 3 binders (Box 151)
    - The Review (bound issues), 1976-1977, 3 binders (Box 152)
    - The Review (bound issues), 1977-1978, 2 binders (Box 153)
    - The Review (bound issues), 1979-1981, 2 binders (Box 154)
    - The Review (bound issues), 1982-1985, 2 binders (Box 155)
    - The Review (bound issues), 1989, 1 binder (Box 156)
    - The Whetstone, 1924-1931, 9 folders (Box 156)
    - The Whetstone, 1932-1939, 13 folders (Box 157)
    - The Whetstone, 1940-1952, 14 folders (Box 158)
    - The Whetstone, 1953-1964, 12 folders (Box 159)
    - The Whetstone, 1965-1977, 13 folders (Box 160)
    - The Whetstone, 1978-1998, 11 folders (Box 161)
    - The Whetstone (bound issues), 1943-1950, 1 binder (Box 161)
    - The Whetstone (bound issues), 1947-1959, 2 binders (Box 162)
    - The Whetstone (binding removed), 1960-1967, 3 folders (Box 163)
    - Miscellaneous publications (bound), 1920-1963, 1 binder (Box 163)
    - The North Carolina Mutual, 1903 Sept., [frame removed]; box size: 20x24 inches (Box OV38)
      [Some of the materials in this box are fragile and in need of preservation. Please contact Research Services to use this material, as contents may need to be reproduced before being handled.]
    - The North Carolina Mutual, 1907 Jan., box size: 14x18 inches (Box OV23)
    - Two pages from internal publication (probably The Mutual) Vol. II, no. 6, between 1907-1918 (photocopies), box size: 14x18 inches (Box OV23)
    - One page (small pieces missing) from unidentified NC Mutual publication (The NC Mutual?), Vol. II, No. 6, 1904; box size: 11x17 inches (Box OV58)
    - Bottom half of page from unidentified NC Mutual publication (NC Mutual?), with additional small fragments, 1906; box size: 11x17 inches (Box OV58)
      Page from what is almost certainly a publication for NC Mutual staff contains aphorisms, inspirational messages, jokes, and news items about staff and policy holders.
  - North Carolina Mutual Life Insurance Company Pamphlets and Other Publications, circa 1917-2008 and undated
    Various publications issued by North Carolina Mutual. The earliest piece, circa 1917, is a pamphlet from the Life Extension Department of NC Mutual, by Medical Director Clyde Donnell, M.D., on the health risks associated with flies, especially the spread of diseases, giving advice on eliminating flies from human inhabitations. Other items include programs from memorial services; publications commemorating company anniversaries and the opening of new offices; The Mutual Album (a booklet containing photographs and biographies of NCM's founders and early employees); Education in our Democracy (a reprint of a speech that W.J. Kennedy, Jr. gave at Fort Valley State College); The Negro's Adventures in the Field of Life Insurance and Partners in Business (instructional tracts written by W.J. Kennedy, Jr. and Asa T. Spaulding, respectively); and various sales, promotional, and recruitment material, and training manuals. Arranged alphabetically by title or subject.
    - Annual Report, 1994, 3 folders (Box 135)
    - Black Achievement calendars, 1977-1979 (Box 135)
    - Charters, bylaws, and resolutions, 1971-1984 (Box 135)
    - Cloudburst All-Stars, 1985 (Box 135)
    - Cruise West Indies and Caribbean, 1961 May (Box 135)
    - Dedication Festival for Mutual Plaza, 1968 March 28-April 2 (Box 135)
    - Education in our Democracy, undated (Box 135)
    - Employee wellness program, 2002 (Box 135)
    - Facts about African Americans pamphlets, undated (Box 135)
    - Founders' days/anniversaries, 1969-2008 (Box 135)
    - Founders Memorial Services, pamphlet, 1983 (Box 135)
    - A Glossary of Insurance and Insurance-Related Terms, circa 1982 (Box 135)
    - Funerals and memorial services, 1944-2005, 2 folders (Box 135)
    - Health bulletin from the Life Extension Department of NC Mutual, Swat The [fly], by Medical Director Clyde Donnell, M.D., circa 1917 (Box 135)
      Cover of this black-and-white, two-page pamphlet has the words "Swat The" and a large hand-drawn illustration of a fly. Four smaller illustrations show sites for the spread of disease: an outhouse, stable, sickroom, and windows with no screens. Donnell was promoted to Medical Director in 1917.
    - Home office ground-breaking/dedication, 1963-1966 (Box 135)
    - Internal promotional material, 1961-1985, 3 folders (Box 135)
    - Internal promotional material, 1985-1987 and undated, 2 folders (Box 185)
    - Living and Working Together the Mutual's Way, employee manual, 1953 (revised ed.) (Box 185)
      Forty-seven page employee manual originally written under the direction of President William J. Kennedy, Jr. in 1949.
    - Music recital program, between 1958 and 1968, 2 copies (Box 185)
    - The Negro's Adventure in the Field of Life Insurance, by William J. Kennedy, Jr., 1934, 1937, 3 folders (Box 185)
      Contains 14-page pamphlet of the history of African American-owned life insurance industry, with multiple copies of 1934 first edition and one second edition copy from 1937. Includes lists of historical and current companies and their assets and expenditures. Three folders hold many duplicate copies, probably to be mailed to other Mutual offices.
    - North Carolina Mutual: A Symbol, 1960-1964 (Box 185)
    - Office openings, 1946-1950 (Box 136)
    - Office and officer images, undated (Box 136)
    - Partners in Business, 1940 (Box 136)
    - Proceedings of the Annual Agents' Conference, 1920 (Box 136)
    - Program honoring Asa Spaulding, 1959 (Box 136)
    - Remington Rand Punched-Card Applications, 1950s? (Box 136)
    - Retirees Anniversary Banquet, pamphlet, 2005 (Box 136)
    - Sales and promotional material, undated, 10 folders (Box 136)
    - Statistical Bulletin, 1923 (Box 136)
    - Training manuals and guides, 1927-1988 and undated, 6 folders (Box 136)
    - You and Your Company handbook, after 1965 (Box 136)
    - Your Career recruitment pamphlet, undated (Box 136)
  - Periodical Clippings, 1906-1996 and undated
    Contains groups of clippings, mostly assembled by the Public Relations Department, from mainstream national and local newspapers, university newspapers, and African American publications. Arranged alphabetically by topic.
    - Civil rights, 1947-1960, 3 folders (Box 173)
    - League of Women Voters, 1950-1953 (Box 173)
    - North Carolina newspapers, 2005 (Box 173)
    - NCM, 1960-1966, 1991, 2 folders (Box 173)
    - Richmond, Tyronza, 1994 (Box 173)
    - Spaulding, C.C., undated (Box 173)
    - Tillotson College, undated (Box 173)
    - Tougaloo Southern Christian College, 1945-1956 (Box 173)
    - Town Hall world tours, 1949-1953 (Box 173)
    - Toure, Sekou, 1959-1961 (Box 173)
    - Tuskegee Institute, AL, 1949-1958 (Box 173)
    - Various topics, 1955-1968, 1984, 3 folders (Box 173)
    - Washington, Booker T., 1946-1960 (Box 173)
    - Washington, George, 1953 (Box 173)
    - Watchtower Life Insurance Company, Houston TX, 1939 (Box 173)
    - Weaver, Robert C., 1961-1962 (Box 173)
    - Wilberforce University, OH, 1949-1956 (Box 173)
    - Wiley College, TX, 1958 (Box 173)
    - William Penn Business School, 1951 (Box 173)
    - Williamsburg VA, 1962 (Box 173)
    - Winston Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1935-1957 (Box 173)
    - Winston-Salem Teachers' College, 1961 (Box 173)
    - Wit and humor (wise sayings), 1948-1955, 2 folders (Box 174)
    - Women of the Week and Year, 1949-1957 (Box 174)
    - Wright, Richard, 1961 (Box 174)
    - WTCU, 1949-1953 (Box 174)
    - Xavier University, 1949-1952 (Box 174)
    - Y-Teens, 1955 (Box 174)
    - Ye Towne on Queen Anne's Creek, 1962 (Box 174)
    - YMCA, 1949-1957 (Box 174)
    - YWCA, 1950-1958 (Box 174)
    - Zeta Phi Beta sorority, 1950-1953 (Box 174)
    - Various topics, oversize clippings, 1955-1967, box size: 16x20 inches (Box OV4)
      [Some of the materials in this box are fragile and in need of preservation. Please contact Research Services to use this material, as contents may require photocopying before being handled.]
    - Various topics, oversize clippings, 1936, 1953, 1964, 1967, 1984, box size: 11x14 inches (Box OV9)
    - Various topics, 1967, 1982, 2006, box size: 14x18 inches (Box OV23)
    - Unknown newspaper article on charges against Dr. Norris, physician for NCM (?), ca. 1928, box size: 14x18 inches (Box OV23)
    - Civil rights, The Picture News, 1947 Nov. 2, box size: 15x19 inches (Box OV35)
    - Various topics, 1984, 1991-1994, 3 folders; box size: 15x19 inches (Box OV35)
    - C.C. Spaulding, 1942 Dec. 12, box size: 15x19 inches (Box OV35)
    - NCM oversize clippings, 1921, 1926, box size: 20x24 inches (Box OV39)
    - Laminated NCM clippings, 1906, 1921, 1966, 1988, box size: 20x24 inches (Box OV39)
    - Kennedy, Jr., W.J., 1952-1958, box size: 20x24 inches (Box OV39)
    - Wheeler, J.L. funeral notices, 1957 Apr. 22, box size: 20x24 inches (Box OV39)
    - Lawsuit and annual meeting, 1972-1973, box size: 20x24 inches (Box OV39)
    - Various topics, 1943-1966, 3 folders; box size: 20x24 inches (Box OV39)
    - Various topics, 1983-1996, 5 folders; box size: 20x24 inches (Box OV39)
      [Some of the materials in this folder are fragile and in need of preservation. Please contact Research Services to use this material, as contents may require photocopying before being handled.]
  - Publications by Other Organizations, 1914-2006 and undated
    - North Carolina Central University (NCCU) Publications
      Material related to North Carolina Central University, including commencement programs, course guides, an issue of the campus journal Varia, issues of the campus newspaper The Echo, and issues of the faculty newsletter The Faculty Fuzz. Includes oversize material, given at end of grouping.
      - Annual school catalog, 1959-1960 (Box 163)
      - Annual school catalog, 1961-1962 (Box 163)
      - Commencement programs, 1959-1964 (Box 163)
      - Summer school, 1951 (Box 163)
      - Miscellaneous publications, 1960-1992 and undated ( (Box 163)
      - Varia journal, 1963 (Box 163)
      - Golden Echo, 1960 Jan.; Campus Echo, 1964 Sept. 28; Alumni Bulletin, 1964 Apr., box size: 14x18 inches (Box OV35)
      - Faculty and Staff Fuzz, 1963, 1965, 5 issues; box size: 14x18 inches (Box OV35)
    - Non-NCM Pamphlets and Other Publications
      Various items related to organizations other than North Carolina Mutual. Includes a large collection of material related to African American history; a number of government publications (primarily concerning either the African American population or the state of the economy); files from a 1973 audit of NCM conducted by the firm Ernst and Ernst; brochures and booklets related to health education; and publications produced by the NAACP, the National Urban League, the Southern Regional Council, the National Insurance Association, the Institute of Life Insurance, Ebony, the United Negro College Fund, the National Council of Negro Women, and the Peace Corps, among many others. Arranged in alphabetical order by title or subject, with oversize material at the end.
      - American Heart Association Pamphlets, undated (Box 164)
      - Annual Report, The National Industrial Conference Board, 1967 (Box 164)
      - Archives*Records, DC, 2006 (Box 164)
      - Atlanta Home Horizons, 1962 (Box 164)
      - Bits and Pieces, undated (Box 164)
      - Blacks and Hispanics in the United States, 1979 (Box 164)
      - American Traveler's Guide to Negro History, undated (Box 164)
      - Arno Press, Black Studies Program catalog, 1972 (Box 164)
      - The Black Presence in North Carolina exhibition program, 1978 (Box 164)
      - Blacks in the Westward Movement, 1975 (Box 164)
      - Calendars, 1983-1985 (Box 164)
      - Fifty Years of Progress pamphlets, 1950 (Box 164)
      - Flags of Famous Black Military Units, 1976 (Box 164)
      - Golden Legacy comic book, 1984 (Box 164)
      - Merzette coloring books, 1985 (Box 164)
      - Negro History Week: A National Celebration, undated (Box 164)
      - Pepper Bird Pathways: African American Heritage, 1995 (Box 164)
      - The Pride and the Passion, 1983 (Box 164)
      - Black Resource Guide, 1983 (Box 164)
      - Blue Cross/Blue Shield of North Carolina annual report, 1994 (Box 164)
      - British and Foreign Anti-Slavery Reporter indices, 1840-1846, 1854, 1857-1860 [photocopies] (Box 164)
      - Business training pamphlets, 1948-1983 and undated (Box 164)
      - Can These Bones Live, by R.V. Horton, 1974 (Box 164)
      - Choose a Career That Counts, 1959 (Box 164)
      - Civil Rights and the South: A Symposium, 1963 (Box 164)
      - Conference Board publications, 1966-1969 and undated, 3 folders (Box 164)
      - Corporate Structure, 1993 (Box 165)
      - Diego Rivera/Mexico tourism material, postcards, undated (Box 165)
      - Durham: A Rare Combinations of Qualities, undated (Box 165)
      - Durham County Almanac, 1925 (Box 165)
      - Ebony Publications on Negro Market Potential, 1965 and undated (Box 165)
      - Ernst and Ernst audit, 1973, 3 folders (Box 165)
      - An Evening with Chuck Davis, program, 1992 (Box 165)
      - Falcon Song, World Expo pamphlet, 1992 (Box 165)
      - Federal Records Centers folder with various pamphlets, leaflets, undated (Box 165)
      - Government publications:
        - Black Americans: A Chartbook, 1971 (Box 165)
        - Causes of Negro Insurance Company Failures, 1937 (Box 165)
        - Committee for Economic Development, 1968-1969 (Box 165)
        - Department of Labor, 1965-1966 (Box 165)
        - Franchise Company Data, 1968 (Box 165)
        - General Services Administration occupancy guides, 1963-1965 (Box 165)
        - National Negro Health Week, 1928 (Box 165)
        - The Negro Woman Worker, 1938 (Box 165)
        - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1967 (Box 165)
        - The Social and Economic Status of the Black Population in the United States, 1972 (Box 165)
        - Third Report of Insurance Companies Owned and Operated by Negroes, 1949 (Box 165)
      - Health education, 1994-1998 and undated, 3 folders (Box 166)
      - History Speaks, 1932 (Box 166)
      - Home Insurance Companies, 1933 (Box 166)
      - In Loving Memory of Mr. Willie C. Lovett program, 1992 (Box 166)
      - Institute of Life Insurance, 1959 and undated (Box 166)
      - The Integration of the Negro into the United States Navy, 1948 (Box 166)
      - Joint Center for Political Studies, 1982 (Box 166)
      - Life Insurance Facts for Business Women, 1956 (Box 166)
      - Martin Luther King and The Montgomery Story, 1956 (Box 166)
      - Musings of a Teenager, Lawrence A. Dunmore, 1974 (Box 166)
      - National Archives brochures, 2005 (Box 166)
      - NAACP publications, 1955-1963, 2 folders (Box 166)
      - National Council of Negro Women, 1956-1981 (Box 166)
      - National Negro Finance Corporation, 1924 (Box 166)
      - National Negro Business League Annual Report, 1914 (Box 166)
      - National Insurance Association member roster, 2002 (Box 166)
      - National Urban League Building for the Future, 1956 (Box 166A)
      - The Negro and the Depression in North Carolina, 1933 (Box 166A)
      - Negro History Week, pamphlet, undated, 2 copies (Box 166A)
      - The Newcomen Society, 1958-1960 (Box 166A)
      - A New Era on Parrish Street pamphlet, circa 2004 (Box 166A)
      - New Directions, reprint, 1974 (Box 166A)
      - North American Reassurance Company Forecast for the Seventies, 1962 (Box 166A)
      - North Carolina AIDS resource directory, 1989 (Box 166A)
      - North Carolina Black Leadership Caucus fifteenth annual conference, 1991 (Box 166A)
      - North Carolina Human Relations Council, 1978 (Box 167)
      - Peace Corps publications, 1961 and undated (Box 167)
      - Physical Distribution: Key Points for Presidents, 1967 (Box 167)
      - Position paper, Allan P. Sindler, undated (Box 167)
      - Preparing the Annual Report, 1960 (Box 167)
      - The Quarterly Earnings Roller Coaster Best's Insurance Review, 1976 (Box 167)
      - Race in the News, circa 1950 (Box 167)
      - Reading Course in Executive Technique, 1948 (Box 167)
      - Register to Vote flier, undated (Box 167)
      - The Road to Justice: Three Major Statements on Civil Rights by President Lyndon B. Johnson, 1965 (Box 167)
      - Russian scholarship, 1952-1955 and undated (Box 167)
      - Society of American Archivists Annual Report, 2005 (Box 167)
      - Southern Regional Council publications, 1960 and undated (Box 167)
      - Stony the Road We Trod...: a Portrait of Black North Carolinians in Prose and Poetry, 1976 Nov. (Box 167)
      - A Survey of the Years 1898-1899, 1958 (Box 167)
      - Tax law information, 1966-1979 (Box 167)
      - They Call Him 'Co-operation,' 1943, 2 copies (Box 167)
      - They Defend Genocide and Cannibalism, remarks of Hon. Claude Pepper, 1965 Feb. 17 (Box 167)
      - Thomas Day, Cabinetmaker exhibition program, 1975, 2 copies (Box 167)
      - Thomas F. Keller Center dedication, 1996 (Box 167)
      - Three Peeps and Some Looks, by J. Mason Brewer, 1963 Jun. (Box 167)
      - Toward the Preservation of a Heritage: Inaugural Exhibition of The Howard University Museum, 1979 (Box 167)
      - Triad Black Business Expo program, 1994 (Box 167)
      - United Negro College Fund, 1958-1964 and undated (Box 167)
      - University of North Carolina commencement, 1967 (Box 167)
      - Urinary Analysis by Chemical Examination, 1923 (Box 167)
      - Vacuum Freeze-Drying, undated (Box 167)
      - Vocational Training Opportunities in North Carolina, 1963 (Box 167)
      - You Can Go Places and See Things in the Life Insurance Business, undated (Box 167)
      - City of Durham master plan report, 1959, box size: 11x14 inches (Box OV14)
      - Cosmopolitan Chamber of Commerce report on Chicago, 1965, box size: 11x14 inches (Box OV14)
      - White Rock Baptist Church: A Brief History, undated, box size: 14x18 inches (Box OV35)
      - NIA national convention, 2003 (Box 188)
    - Non-NCM Serials
      Serials published by other entities, chiefly newspapers. Includes early issues of Durham, N.C. African American and other local newspapers (1906-1945), and many issues of The Journal of Negro History and The Pilot, official journal of the National Negro Insurance Association. Arranged in alphabetical order by title.
      - Administrative Management, 1967 Mar. (Box 167)
      - American Magazine, 1948 Dec. (Box 167)
      - American Visions, 1990 June (Box 167)
      - The Atlantic, 1940 May (Box 167)
      - Best's Insurance News, 1943-1967 (Box 167)
      - Best's Life Rating Chart, 1928, 1930 (Box 168)
      - Blackbook, 1983 (Box 168)
      - Black Business Digest, 1973 May (Box 168)
      - Black Business Ink, 2003 Aug. (Box 168)
      - Black Enterprise, 1974-1993, 4 folders (Box 168)
      - Black Scholar, 1987 July/Aug./Sept./Oct. (Box 168)
      - Black Southerner Magazine, 1982 (Box 168)
      - The Brown American, 1958 Fall (Box 168)
      - Business Automation, 1964 Sept. (Box 168)
      - Business Leader, 1991 Oct. (Box 168)
      - Campus Echo, 1957 Feb. 28 (photocopy), box size: 14x18 inches (Box OV36)
      - The Carolina Times, 1966 Mar. 5, 19, 26, Apr. 9; 1968 Dec. 14; 1994 Sept. 24, box size: 20x24 inches (Box OV38)
      - The Carolinian, 1983 Feb. 17, box size: 20x24 inches (Box OV38)
      - Caravan, 1965 April/May (Box 168)
      - Chicago Daily Defender, 1965 Dec. 8-9, box size: 14x18 inches (Box OV36)
      - Chief Legal Executive, Winter 2003 (Box 168)
      - Concrete Facts, undated (Vol. 12 #2) (Box 168)
      - Concrete Products, 1965 May (Box 168)
      - Council Review, 1985 Apr./May-Sept. (Box 168)
      - The Crisis, 1931-1968, 2 folders (Box 168)
      - Dollars and Sense, 1983-1986 (Box 168)
      - Double Ought, 1999 Nov.-2000 Oct., box size: 20x24 inches (Box OV38)
      - Durham Morning Herald, 1966 Mar. 12, Apr. 3; 1968 May 5; 1981 Apr. 26, box size: 20x24 inches (Box OV38)
      - Durham Morning Herald, 1927 July 3 (photocopied by NCM), box size: 20x24 inches (Box OV38)
        Contains article about Royal Knights of King David, Durham.
      - Durham Negro Observer (5 issues), 1906 June-October; box size: 18x24 inches (Box OV59)
      - The Durham News Journal, 1966 Mar. 31, box size: 20x24 inches (Box OV38)
      - Durham Report, undated (Box 168)
      - The Durham Sun, 1921 Dec. 31 (photocopy), box size: 14x18 inches (Box OV36)
      - The Durham Sun (three full pages, small pieces lacking), 1945 August 29; box size: 18x24 inches (Box OV59)
      - The Durham Sun, 1966 Mar. 31, box size: 21x25 inches (Box OV38)
      - Durham YMCA Heartbeats, 1994 Apr. (Box 168)